https://www.nhlp.org/about/privacy-statement-return-policy/

Close About Board Contact Mission Housing Justice Network Housing Justice Network Conference Opportunities at NHLP Staff Support NHLP What We Do Privacy Statement and Return Policy COVID 19 Resource Center Federal Budget Public Housing Section 8 Housing Choice Vouchers Project-Based Vouchers Project-Based Rental Assistance Section 202 and Section 811 Programs for the Elderly or Persons with Disabilities Low-Income Housing Tax Credits USDA Rural Housing Programs Initiatives Saving Affordable Homes Housing Voucher Utilization Protections for Survivors of Domestic and Sexual Violence Nuisance and Crime-Free Ordinances Initiative Immigrant Rights Fair Housing & Housing for People with Disabilities Housing Opportunities for People Reentering Healthy Housing Tenants and Foreclosure Utility Allowances, Energy-Efficiency, and Renewables in Affordable Housing Trainings & Publications NEW! Green Book Digital Library Webinars Purchase NHLP Publications Companion Website - HUD Housing Programs: Tenants' Rights NHLP Publications Advocacy & Litigation Advocacy Litigation Support NHLPInitiativesHome » About » Privacy Statement and Return PolicyPrivacy Statement and Return PolicyPrivacy Policy The National Housing Law Project is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about the type of information we collect when you visit nhlp.org (“our website”) and to explain the manner in which we collect, store, maintain and protect that information.Information we collect When you visit our website you may provide us with three types of information: personal information you voluntarily disclose through website features, aggregate or statistical use information collected as you browse our website, and information you voluntarily provide whenever communicating electronically with us.Personal information We offer a number of features through our website for your convenience such as registration forms, donation forms, and contact forms. Whenever you choose to use these features, you may disclose “personal information” including your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, and preferences. In order to serve you, we collect and store this personal information on an individual basis. We do not collect any credit card information through our website. Credit card payments are processed externally through a third-party vendor which ensures the security and confidentiality of your financial information.Website use information Our website utilizes standard technology to read and write “cookies” and to generate web server logs. These technologies collect information about your use of our website. This information may include the date and time of visits, your internet protocol address, the pages you view on our site, time you spent at our website, information about your web browser and operating system, and location of the website visited just before our website. None of this information is directly associated with any personal information you provide to us, and we make no attempt to relate such information to your personal information.Donor Information NHLP does not trade, share or sell an online or offline donor’s personal information with anyone else nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.Other electronic communication If you send us any electronic communication, including e-mail, we may retain your e-mail message together with your email address and our responses.How we use that information We use personal information and information obtained by electronic communication solely for our own organizational activities and our interactions with you.We will not sell, rent, or lease any of your personal information.We may use the aggregate or statistical website use information for security and maintenance purposes to improve our website and to better serve our visitors.How we protect that information Because we value your privacy, we are dedicated to protecting the personal information you provide to us by adhering to the following procedures.Our business practices We routinely monitor our business practices for compliance with this policy and any other procedures regarding security, confidentiality, and accuracy of our information.Access to information We limit our employees’ access to your personal information, and we restrict any use or disclosure of personal information to authorized individuals, processes, or transactions.Required disclosure of personal information We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.How you can reach us If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact Susan Stern, NHLP Deputy Director, sstern@nhlp.org.Return & Refund Policy Thanks for shopping at NHLP.orgIf you are not entirely satisfied with your purchase, we’re here to help.Returns You have 30 calendar days to return an item from the date you received it.To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it.Your item needs to have the receipt or proof of purchase.Refunds Once we receive your item, we will inspect it and notify you that we have received your returned item. We will immediately notify you on the status of your refund after inspecting the item.If your return is approved, we will initiate a refund to your credit card (or original method of payment).You will receive the credit within a certain amount of days,depending on your card issuer’s policies.Shipping You will be responsible for paying for your own shipping costs for returning your item. Shipping costs are nonrefundable.If you receive a refund, the cost of return shipping will be deducted from your refund.Contact Us If you have any questions on how to return your item to us, contact Wendy Mahoney, wmahoney@nhlp.org About
Board Contact Mission Housing Justice Network Housing Justice Network Conference Opportunities at NHLP Staff Support NHLP What We Do Privacy Statement and Return Policy COVID 19 Resource Center
Federal Budget Public Housing Section 8 Housing Choice Vouchers Project-Based Vouchers Project-Based Rental Assistance Section 202 and Section 811 Programs for the Elderly or Persons with Disabilities Low-Income Housing Tax Credits USDA Rural Housing Programs Initiatives
Saving Affordable Homes Housing Voucher Utilization Protections for Survivors of Domestic and Sexual Violence Nuisance and Crime-Free Ordinances Initiative Immigrant Rights Fair Housing & Housing for People with Disabilities Housing Opportunities for People Reentering Healthy Housing Tenants and Foreclosure Utility Allowances, Energy-Efficiency, and Renewables in Affordable Housing Trainings & Publications
NEW! Green Book Digital Library Webinars Purchase NHLP Publications Companion Website - HUD Housing Programs: Tenants' Rights NHLP Publications Advocacy & Litigation
Advocacy Litigation Support NHLPShareThisRelated Content NHLP Praises HEROES Act Introduction, Calls for Strong Congressional Oversight Statement by Shamus Roller, Executive Director of the National Housing Law Project Today, Speaker Pelosi introduced a $3
NHLP Analysis of HUD’s Public and Indian Housing Waiver Notice NHLP Analysis of HUD’s Public and Indian Housing Waiver Notice This is NHLP’s analysis
NHLP Submits Comments on HUD’s “Equal Participation of Faith-Based Organizations” Rule The National Housing Law Project submitted comments this April to oppose HUD’s “Equal Sign Up For Our newsletter
First NameLast NameEmail* CommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
